{
    "id": "fda80d9d85934ad88bfe8be55388898d",
    "title": "Identify The Adjective",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The cake baking in the oven made the whole house fragrant.",
            "description": "It modifies the noun house.",
            "answers": [
                "cake",
                "oven",
                "fragrant"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5ad94bf1ef7c4f809d2d4d2c69b17297"
        },
        {
            "question": "The climber dangled in midair, held by a frail rope.",
            "description": "It modifies the noun rope.",
            "answers": [
                "dangled",
                "midair",
                "frail"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6514c00611a8460cbe31bb182eb75b3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a lot of frantic activity just before the arrival of royal visitors.",
            "description": "It modifies the noun activity.",
            "answers": [
                "lot",
                "before",
                "frantic"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ec9e1c1fb76949119a30e204f9d9892e"
        },
        {
            "question": "There was always a lot of fraternal affection between the boys.",
            "description": "It modifies the noun affection.",
            "answers": [
                "always",
                "fraternal",
                "between"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f414e45b53a649de9a5aaf28cde12c3b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The puppy flopped around on the slippery floor.",
            "description": "It modifies the noun floor.",
            "answers": [
                "puppy",
                "around",
                "slippery"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3f3ec98b08d94f09839c47cce0993924"
        },
        {
            "question": "The wallpaper had a floral pattern.",
            "description": "It modifies the noun pattern.",
            "answers": [
                "wallpaper",
                "floral",
                "pattern"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "31371ffb7b094dbf992712022898f1c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The shop sells ice-cream in eight different flavors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shop",
                "eight",
                "different"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5d889ce8303541dfa22f89e8b5a262b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Lack of civilian clothes was the one flaw in our escape plan.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "civilian",
                "one",
                "escape",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "615d63c04f87441c886f0ba7a49dc3ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "The hot coals made a fizzle as they hit the water.",
            "description": "It modifies the noun coals.",
            "answers": [
                "hot",
                "fizzle",
                "water"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "38a54db154f24c23934ed6bc934a3e1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "That was a flagrant abuse of his authority.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "flagrant",
                "authority"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8758e45815ed46d280cbbd37dd4248f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "This new medication fills an urgent need.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "medication",
                "new",
                "urgent",
                "need"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0414e340dcfa408f9eb828991d3f2c22"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our final meeting for the season is next Wednesday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "final",
                "season",
                "next"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5b1cd822c85e45c5b708bcfcf952654a"
        }
    ]
}